You ain't really with me way back
then, but how about now? Cuz I'm up
right now.
And you suck right now.
Aw, you thought you had it all figured
out back then, girl. [music] How about
now? Cuz I'm up right now.
And you suck right now.
Yeah. You thought the little effort that
you put in was enough, girl. How about
now?
Yeah.
Girl, [music] how about now? Ladies and
gentlemen, welcome How about now, girl?
How about now, girl? How about now,
girl? How about now, girl?
So cool.
Give me Give me the dogs going crazy.
Like, what the
That is so cool. That's the way
to make the entrance. I have always
always wanted to do that. Land the
helicopter in my backyard. Well,
technically, this is my front lawn.
>> [music]
>> For the Set and Forget Estate, ladies
and gentlemen. A big warm welcome,
ladies and gentlemen, to the Set and
Forget Trading Floor Compound HQ. I
don't know what to name it yet. I have
no idea. And that's what you guys are
here for. I want you guys to help me to
name this building. So, the purpose of
this building is going to be a massive
trading floor. And we're going to do a
big parking lot here for when guests
come over. Paintball field, we're going
to do right here. Basketball court,
pickleball court, tennis court. Why all
three courts? What else do I do with all
this land? The drift track is
going to be right here. All this area,
we're going to actually come over here.
We're going to take out that building,
do another steel building,
outdoor gym, horse stables,
and so much more. So,
this is it.
This is it, ladies and gentlemen. If you
If you guys are new to the channel, if
you guys don't know who I am, I was
working at Dunkin' Donuts probably
around like 7 and 1/2 years ago now. And
I came from a very average household
income. My parents made probably
combined 100 120,000 dollars a year.
Right in the middle of middle class.
That sounds crazy for the rest of the
world.
>> Yeah, like I was like literally in the
middle of the middle class. Like my
parents made very very healthy income. I
we had everything that we needed to
live. I'm probably going to be all in
when I'm done with this, like 6 million
dollars. So, let's just say I paid 6
million dollars for this. And this is my
sixth property, actually. I have this, I
have the two lots where I'm building
homes on, which is a whole other story
because I was going to build one big
house, my dream house on it, but the
permits didn't let me, so I had to split
the lots in half, do one on one house. I
have uh three apartments. And the
probably my my my best property that
I've acquired is my dad's house. My dad
didn't believe in me that I was able to
do something. And uh you know, stuff
happened in in life and
I had to get him a house. So, let's just
say that he definitely believes me now.
So, it's his house, but it's my house.
So, I have seven properties. I guess you
could you could include the Bugatti as a
property. Yeah, I think I think Bugatti
counts as a house.
>> 3 million dollars.
>> I think the Jacob & Co., too.
>> Cash. I mean, the Jacob & Co. is like a
cheap house. It's like a Can't even say
it.
>> People say I come off like a douchebag
online. Why? I'm a very chill guy.
You're you're saying that you made like
a a very humble amount as a household
income of 100,000 dollars for the rest
of the world.
>> For for for America. For America.
>> You got to clarify that part. Okay,
okay. What is the average household
income in America, in the United States?
Imagine an Italian watching this thing,
100,000 dollars a year. Look, medium
household income in the United States
was approximately 80,000 dollars in
2023.
That's combined. So, that's the mom and
the dad. So, we were like a right around
100. So, I'd say we're on the little bit
higher end of middle class. we
ain't got Bugatti money. Now we do, you
know? So, yeah, this is uh I was going
to get very creative and I was going to
put set and forget here
uh because we're we're we're going to
obviously paint the building black.
We're pressure washing and doing all
that, but right as my handwriting is not
that good,
so I I cut it short. When I know I'm I'm
wrong with something, I I don't keep
going with it. I ate I'm I'm wrong. It's
it's done there. So, I cut it at the
what kind of looks like a T.
Which looks more like like an X, right?
So ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the
official trading floor. There's a whole
lot of nothing here.
>> Yeah, for now. Pop up the render right
here.
So this is what it's going to look like.
Give or take. Maybe we're going to add
some stuff, remove some stuff. And then
over there, right right over here, Lito?
On the other side of those mango trees
and those aguacate trees, we're going to
move them. We're going to re We'll go
over there. Now actually let's hear one
thing at a time. I'm I'm I'm getting too
ahead of myself.
>> Yeah, this property is a little too big
for us.
>> I'm getting way too ahead of myself. One
thing at a time. This is going to be a
mix of my personal office, uh traders
that I want to be cool with. Rocky, get
Get out of here. You're too loud. Get.
Go.
Get out of here. So for me, this HQ is
is to bring traders together. And
traders that are serious traders, really
want to work with other cool traders, be
part of an environment. I remember when
I started trading, I would see these
traders in the UK that they had their
own trading floor in the UK. And
everybody was just trading, breaking
down markets, uh discussing why they
should enter a trade or not. They were
all managing a pool of money. And it was
just like the environment that you want
to be in because as a trader, it's a
very lonely journey. And it's just you
and your computer screen late at night,
you and your computer screen early in
the morning, and you really don't have
anybody to feed back and forth. And yes,
you can you can send a Zoom link with
somebody and break something down,
[music] but it's never the same as if
you were to be in person while you're
you're surrounded with like-minded
people. I've always had that same idea
to do the same thing here in Miami. My
my version of it, right? Adding the
drift track, the paintball field, adding
everything that makes it me and makes it
Miami. And I finally did it. And this is
where I plan to have five, six, seven
traders to be trading here. We're going
to uh work towards one single goal. This
is my first time ever announcing this. I
am tired of the whole social media
dilemma that oh, this guy Alex is just a
course seller. He's just a trader that
sells courses. That's how he makes his
money. Wrong. I'm actually a
fantastic trader. I'm a very good trader
and I'm going to show people how good I
am. Not by doing another account flip,
not by passing a prop firm, not by doing
a small challenge, by starting a fund.
I'm going to be starting a fund, ladies
and gentlemen. My goal is to have half a
billion dollars under management and in
here is where I'm going to work to get
my license so I get all of my
regulations, all of my paperwork with
the NFA, with my Series 33, 34. I'm
still figuring out exactly which ones I
need so I'm able to manage that amount
of money. I saw the other day that one
of the top funds in the world have
returns of 25% annually, 35, 40%
annually. I'm like, dude, that is
literally nothing. That's like 3% a
month, 4% a month. That is so doable. I
can do that by taking
one trade a month, maybe two trades a
month. Let's say I take one loss and one
win. That one win will make back all
that loss and have that profit for the
month, which will be the will be the
goal. My next goal, my purpose in the
next two, three, four, five, six, 10
years is to acquire half a billion
dollars under management. And in here,
alongside with the traders that I have
in this trading floor, we're all going
to be working to achieve that together.
So I'm building a hedge fund and this is
where we're going to do it, straight out
of this HQ. We're going to have traders
in the bottom, we're going to have
lounge areas in the top. And I also want
to do this because people have a
misconception of what a real profitable
trader on Wall Street is or they have to
have a certain attire or they have to
stand up to a certain standard. That's
right? Like like traders on
Wall Street, they have suit and ties,
they speak a certain way and that's why
they're profitable traders because
they're educated. I think that's
completely false. I think there's a new
era of profitable generational traders
that will come and represent in the next
10, 20 years. And if you want to post
online they're living a crazy life, you
can do that. Like why not? Like how like
the real profitable traders from Wall
Street, they're having these crazy lives
and they're having fun. They're just not
posting about it because, you know, it's
just not it was not part of their
generation. For us, it is, you know,
it's it's it's fun to do cool and
post about it. But, the guys from Wall
Street are probably the most degenerate
guys on the face of the earth. They just
don't post about it. And if I have a
cool degenerate life outside of the
office, that has no association with my
results in the markets. And that's what
I'm going to be the pioneer of and
showing people that you can separate
both very well. Now, this is really like
my first stepping stone to becoming a
billionaire. What, you're going to stop
at 99999999?
No. I think you missed a nine, by the
way. Nine? No, honestly, I I don't think
I'd ever really want to become a
billionaire. I feel like the more money,
more problems. That's 100% facts. And I
feel like anything after 100 million,
it really is just stuff that are bigger
and better. And I don't chase bigger and
better things. I chase like funner and
cooler stuff. I don't think you need
more than that. But, whatever. The
reason why I'm doing this is because
like I feel like I feel partially
responsible for this. That's like the
whole narrative and the stigma around
trading has really turned into about
making money and about being a
degenerate. And and I know I'm just
saying I'm trying to become a half a
billionaire, and I'm just contradicting
myself saying that trading has become
about money, and this is not about
money. Whatever. What I'm trying to say
is the narrative around trading has been
aggressive account flips, which I've
done plenty in the past, which has come
fast in the prop firm as fast as
possible, having the best win rate, the
best everything. And the problem with
that is that it's possible to have these
account flips and to pass these prop
firms, but it's very challenging. If you
look at the Wall Street guys, if you
look at the guys managing these hundreds
of millions of dollars, they're making,
call it, 22%
a year, right? They're making 22% a
year. If you divide that by 12 months,
that would be 1.8%
a month. For all my traders out there
that know how to trade, imagine you had
to make 1.8% a month for you to make
whatever goal you want. Let's say you
want to make $10,000 a month. Let's say
you want to make $5,000 a month. Let's
say your goal is to make 1.8% a month.
How stressless will trading be?
You won't look to trade every single
day, right? You won't look to take every
opportunity the market gives you. You're
going to be very selective about every
trade. Well, that's when I realized when
I got tired of having these aggressive
trades for no reason to make profit for
the month. I said, "You know what? I
want to do something similar to the wash
you guys. Let me break down what they
do." And they they have these
longer-term positions. They have these
longer-term mindsets. They have
positions that hedge each other. And and
it it it's odd just makes sense as to
why they're able to manage so much
amount of money and why they're
profitable year after year. Not saying
that regular trading is not the way to
be profitable, but it's just so much
stressful. So, I I actually have a plan
on how I'm going to acquire this half a
billion dollars. Let me
>> All Let me Let me break it down.
I I
I have to show you.
It's already
>> [laughter]
>> recording here. All right, look. This is
how I plan to acquire
half a billion dollars. So, about a
month ago I recorded a video for my
friends and family, very successful
friends that I've been able to become
friends over the last couple of months.
And I'm and I'm very blessed and honored
to be able to be in a position like this
to have great people around me, very
successful people. This motivates me to
get better and I hope this inspires you
to do the same, to get out of your
comfort zone and go meet other
successful people. There's nothing fun
about being successful by yourself. So,
over the last couple of years, months
I've I've had very great friends and I
said, "You know what? All my friends got
money." And all my friends want
to make more money and they've always
asked me, "How can I make them money?"
But I haven't been able to do that for
them because I don't have my license and
I honestly I never had this idea before.
Now is when I believe I am able to do
it. But I don't want to do it until I
can't prove myself first. So, what I
did, I recorded a video about a month
ago and I sent them to them this video.
I said, "All right. This is just I'm
going to summarize it right now. Hey
guys, this is my $100,000 account right
now. I have deposited into a regulated
broker. I want people to say, "You trade
on regulated broker." No, dude. I trade
on like five different brokers. I trade
on 1X, LQH, OANDA, I trade on forex.com
and I trade on IC Markets. I trade on
all these different brokers because I
like the high leverage of the
unregulated brokers or slightly less
regulated brokers. And I like the
legitimacy for something like this of a
regulated broker. So my reasoning to
deposit here, which is pretty cool by
the way. I deposited 100,000 into here
and they actually paid me $145 in
interest in like 2 weeks. I haven't
obviously traded in in the account. So
what I recorded for my very successful
friends and family was like, "Hey look,
this year for me, 2026, is me building
my trading floor, finding the best
possible traders, and creating a track
record for myself." My goal is to make
20% in the next 12 months. And I want to
send this to you now as I am doing it
beforehand. So as I'm getting my
license, as I'm building everything,
when I come to you a year from now, my
results would have spoken for themselves
and it's just it's an easier
conversation rather than me have to
begin a storytelling. It's like, "Hey,
remember that video I sent you a year
ago of me explaining, hey, this is my
goal. If I reach this goal, I'm going to
open up my fund." Well, it's done. So
right now you're very really much seeing
the early stages of the fund that has no
name. This is the fund right here.
It's not really much of a fund. At least
we have a bicycle. This is it.
>> [laughter]
>> I got to have any, you know? But this is
a very humbling experience. It's like
building something from scratch again.
And I'm basing it off of purely results.
The fund does not open if I don't make
20% on this 100,000 in the next 12
months on forex.com, which is a
regulated broker. Oh, by the way, why
did I go with forex.com? It's the most
regulated broker in the US. So for that
way, anybody that wants to say anything,
it's not real.
Shut up. So that's my plan as to how I
plan to acquire half a billion because I
plan to send updates over the quarters
to people as like, "Hey look, just
letting you know, I'm almost done
getting my license. I have two great
traders in my trading floor and the
results are about 6% right now by the
end of Q1 or whatever they are." And you
know, you you take people through your
journey, you show them the transparency
behind it, and then that within itself
will get spread amongst other people,
and then I will open my doors to the
fund, and then have new people that
would like to join be part of it. I
don't know yet what the profit split
You stepped on the fund, dude.
This is part of the fund, man.
Trash? No, dude. This is uh art.
>> Oh, I I see it. I see the vision.
This is the guy that's going to be
managing half a billion
>> [laughter]
>> And this is going to be This is the guy
helping out.
You know what? We're going to be the
first ones to do it. And I honestly, I
feel like these wealthy guys are just
like us, bro. They're just not as
transparent of how they are personally.
I feel like they have to put a persona
to be who they want to be in front of
their investors. So, like that. I'm
going to be myself at all times. I want
you to be fully confident with me. So,
yeah. I I don't know yet profit split.
It's going to be 80/20, 70/30. I don't
know I don't know I don't know anything
yet, right? All I know is that this is
my plan. This is what I am challenging
myself to do. I'm going to be building
something super cool for great traders
that want to come here. I'll host events
occasionally once a month privately for
my members that are part of my
community. And just honestly, have a
have a spot where traders can just be
themselves. And we can have a ton
of fun while doing it.
So, welcome to the
Give me a name. Swing Trading Lab
Trading Floor?
Sedum Forget Estate? Uh something else?
Uh The Compound? The HQ? Drop comment
ideas down below. That would really
help. The names for the trading floor,
not for the fund. The fund we'll figure
that out. I want you guys to get out of
your comfort zone and have a bigger
picture. Have a bigger vision. Becoming
a profitable trader is not passing a
prop firm account. Passing a prop firm
account is really only the tip of the
iceberg. A profitable trader is not if
you successfully made uh profits for 1
month or even for 1 quarter. It's
building a system. It's building
something that will make you these
consistent profits month over month over
month. And it's not actually like a
dollar amount of money that will make
you profitable. The most important thing
to me, personally, and I could be wrong.
This is my humble opinion, of actually
being labeled a profitable trader, is
knowing exactly what you're doing. Like
knowing exactly why you entered a trade,
why you did not enter a trade, and the
exact reason as to why you risked a
certain amount. And knowing the real
facts behind it, not just saying, "Oh, I
bought this because I was only available
to be in front of the markets at 3:00
p.m. because it's when I got a break
from work." That's not a profitable
trader. You just got involved when you
were able to get involved. It It really
comes down to knowing exactly where you
are and where you want to be. And then
you work backwards there. Okay, so I
want to have half a billion dollars in
the management. Okay, well, how would it
make the most sense to get there? Well,
I can't acquire if I don't have
results. Okay, so I need to get results
first before I can think about pitching
this to anybody. Well, if I just pitched
to somebody this, an empty idea,
nobody's going to believe in me. No
one's going to trust in me. There's
There's no journey. They They didn't
They weren't part of something. So, that
won't work. Well, let me bring them on a
journey. Is it a slower grind on my end?
Would it take longer on my end? Yes. But
this is a quote that Rick Ross said. And
I I I listen to this all the time. Now,
I've heard this guy I know he said he's
he's sort of random quote again. No, no,
no, but bro, Rick Ross, he's bro, he
preaches all the time, but there's this
one thing he said.
You got to do it in his voice so it
sounds right.
>> Actually, I have to go find it cuz I
forgot it.
Is it the one where he goes, "Oh!" No,
it's not that one.
>> ever with me shooting in the gym? I'd
rather move slow.
Let me go find it, bro. Is this one? Is
this one? I don't want to I don't want
to move fast. I want to move correctly.
I just don't want to waste no time. If
it take If it's something that's going
to take us a year to make, if it's
something that's going to take us 10
years to make, that's fine. Long as we
don't waste no time.
Longevity.
Longevity. I'm I don't want to move
fast.
>> Longevity.
>> [laughter]
>> Now, honestly, I I I took probably like
half of that, which is I don't care if
it takes time, I want to move correctly.
That's it. Will it take me a year, maybe
even 2 years to have the results for me
to feel confident to acquire investors?
Sure. but I'm doing it correctly. I'm
having my space. I'm having traders
hedge my positions. I'm more comfortable
with it. I'm bringing people with the
journey. So, what I wanted to It's It's
just me show giving you my example. So,
I'm reverse engineering where I want to
be. And that's exactly what you need to
do. Where do you want to be? Not next
month, not make a certain amount of
money to pay your bills, not a certain
amount of money to get your dream car.
Like have a real long-term vision. Like
I've been wanting this what exactly what
I'm in right now. The moment I got in
started in trading 7 years ago. So, I've
been constantly working to this always
reverse engineering every single step to
get to where I am now. And that's
exactly what you need to do to get where
it is that you want to be. Just a
Alex G motivation and a message.
>> I feel very motivated now.
>> Yeah.
Longevity. Come on, do do it with me.
Longevity.
>> [laughter]
>> Now that we broke that down, let me
actually give you guys like a full
breakdown. All right, I just had to I
really wanted to give you guys my my
vision, right? I really wanted you guys
to feel me. So, from this point right
here, this is like the halfway point of
the building. So, this is about 4,500 sq
ft, give or take. And there's going to
be a second floor right here. There's
going to be an 8-ft So, I'm I'm 6'3. So,
the 8 ft is probably like right here.
We're going to have a I I think tall
guys going to cut his head off in there.
>> we're going to take off the fan. Don't
worry about that. No, we we will
We're fine. We'll be fine. Trust. Yeah,
we're fine, but what if I What if I'm
wearing like some designer No, you'll be
fine. We're going to take off the fan.
Don't worry. We'll be fine. Then we're
going to have a second floor here. Um
offices throughout up here. There'll
probably be like some cubicles, like
breakout rooms and meeting rooms in this
area here. Haven't really figured it out
yet. Maybe a kitchen lounge area in this
section over here. I might or might not
have a glass here, so it just separates
hangout area from trading floor space.
Obviously, over here there's going to be
some trading floors. Over here, I do
want to have a big screen. So, I want to
have like six 50-in TVs make like one
big projected screen. It's better than a
projector. Or might not. Or one of those
big LED screens. And there'll just like
one big table and everybody can break it
down. More of like a lounge area over
here. I don't know. Obviously, the more
I spend more time I spend in here, the
more time changes. You have to
paint these brown
steel color
beams, which I don't like. Oh, also, so
right now we're on the outside. I I'm
planning on potentially painting it
black. It's a It building's fully
insulated, so it won't overheat, which
is totally fine. I don't know if we can
do it black, like a Nardo gray. I don't
know.
Uh we have a lot of space over here on
the side. So, right now we have the
pressure washer. The guys are going to
pressure wash it. I don't know if we do
like a pergola, make like an outdoor
lounge area. I don't know yet. Right I'm
still kind of figuring all this out.
We're going to clean all this stuff now.
Um
That looks like a bonfire.
I don't know. I don't know who did that.
Um over here though, as soon as you walk
out, our plan as of right now
is to have basketball court,
pickleball court,
tennis court. Is there another type of
court that we can have?
Hockey. I don't know.
>> Hockey, yeah. Dude, that's a
great idea, bro. By the way, I've I've
bought plenty of real estate properties
in my life. I think the seller was
getting seller's remorse, and he didn't
want to sell the property. I mean, look
at this. This is a beautiful piece of
property. I I I get it. And it was the
most difficult thing I have ever done in
my life in terms of buying something.
Imagine paying full asking price as to
something that you're selling, and the
person comes in, already approved by the
bank. They come in like I got approved,
I think it was 18 days. I was fully
ready to close in 18 days.
The dude stretched it out for about 4
months, the whole entire selling
process. I don't know why. Man, was this
a mission to buy. Now that Now that it's
mine, I feel like I won. I
conquered, you know? It was bad. He
called the cops on me, said I was
trespassing his property. It was
a mission. So, right here we have
I think this is our avocado tree. I'm
not sure. We have a massive mango tree.
This in mango season will easily give us
100 200 mangoes without a doubt. There's
already a little little ones forming.
Another mango tree and I walk out the
tree, avocado tree. Not your little
Tic Tac black avocados. I'm talking
about like when I walk out them. Pop up
a picture when I walk out them, bro.
It's like some huge green ones. Those
those are the best ones out. So all of
these trees sadly we're going to have to
we're going to have to nuke them. No,
we're going to relocate them. We're
going to we're going to put them
somewhere else because the warehouse
that I plan to have here. I don't know.
Maybe maybe we leave them. Maybe there's
like a nice separation in between one
warehouse and the other and the
basketball courts gives it a little bit
of life. I don't know yet. This is
probably the most up part about
this whole entire property. This
Now this is the problem Rocky.
The problem is that that's my Hey no no
no no don't don't step on him. Don't
step
This
That that was that was Rocky.
This is Rocky now.
Well this is the new version of Rocky.
>> Rocky bro and it's it's kind of
Don't don't don't Okay clarification
clarify cuz people might get confused.
Yeah so the the last owner Yeah I know.
This is this is still my same Rocky. The
last owner had a dog named Rocky
and uh yeah he passed away. He had an
accident or whatever and he's in here.
And my dog's name is Rocky. That's why
it's up. He's a German Shepherd
too, you know. What's the right thing to
do? Should we leave him here?
Yo knowing that guy, bro. He probably
didn't even dig a hole, bro. It's
probably like right there.
>> [laughter]
>> If we probably lift this up we probably
going to see the dog. man. So in
here
we got a little extra barn. We have it
as a storage right now for our Miatas
and all the tires and all the that
we got. But this is most likely going to
get demolished cuz we will be doing the
bigger building. The bigger building is
going to be a combination of a car
collection that I'm actually going to
begin my car collection. I'm actually
going to collect very bespoke cars, very
unique cars, low mile cars, cars that
actually go up in value. So there's
actually a whole car market that it's
pretty much an asset that is an
appreciating asset over time. As long as
you don't drive it, you don't put miles
on it, and it's a very unique type of
spec, these cars will go up in value. I
actually have three cars already that
I've purchased, and they're just sitting
at my boy Carriemotorcars' warehouse cuz
I don't want to have it here. Knowing
me,
I'll be out in the sun and driving it.
So, when I build the actual new barn
that I'm going to do, in there it's
going to be half garage for collecting
the cars, half of it commercial-size
gym. Commercial indoor gym with more
machines than LA Fitness. Over
here there's another barn, which is like
a
maids headquarters is what it was, and
that's going to completely get removed.
Right here is going to go a big
5,000-6,000 sq ft building. Sadly, this
tree is going to have to go. This is
actually a invasive tree. These trees
grow like wildfire, and they grow very
big, and they do nothing but take up
space and drop leaves. How the do
these things give oxygen?
We kind of forgot that important part.
Dude, we don't
we don't use oxygen.
We live in a simulation, bro. We don't
Oxygen is is a myth. You don't have to
breathe. The government made up that
conspiracy. It's not a real thing, bro.
I don't know how this palm tree
grew here. Like,
how did How did that happen? Maybe this
is like a sentimental tree to him.
[music]
To the owner.
I have an idea.
I'm going to chop it off. Let me get the
chainsaw.
All right, Walter. Walter, you wanted to
make my life a pain in the ass
to sell me this property?
This looks like it was your sacred
[music] tree next to your whatever, BUT
YOU, WALTER.
I DON'T THINK IT'LL DO MUCH. SHE'S A LOT
HOTTER THAN A HOW ABOUT THAT?
>> [laughter]
YOU, WALTER.
SOMEONE WOULD PAY GOOD money for that
palm tree. Yeah, honestly, that This is
probably probably a $2,000 palm tree,
bro. Oh, man, I shouldn't have never
done that. No, honestly, I could have
never looked at it the same. Should we
just cut it again? Don't let your HEAT
CONSUME YOU.
OH
>> [laughter]
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT. SO
YEAH, SO this barn
will be getting removed. It looks like
we bought this property from Walter
White if anything. dude. But over
here, so the the other warehouse should
[music] end somewhere around here, start
way back over there. And then from here
this way there will be like an outdoor
seating area. And then right here, right
right here. We're going to be an actual
outdoor gym.
Kind of uh kind of had like kind of
those CrossFit outdoor gyms where it's
like calisthenics stuff, some machines
that could get obviously rain and stuff.
That's going to be over here. I'm going
to have a beach volleyball or
potentially potentially, hypothetically
I might create a pond. So this is
this is labeled as agricultural. So I
can actually make a pond here because of
my agricultural exemption.
And then way over there in the front I
just don't want to walk over there.
Over within the front I'm going to do my
my horse stables, round pen more over
there, little bonfire area right around
here.
So yeah, a lot of a lot of a lot of work
to do.
These are my tires for the monster
truck. These things are huge.
>> even They don't even know you had a
monster truck.
>> Yeah, so I bought a monster truck on
Facebook Marketplace just to buy it. So
this this is the size of the tire.
And honestly, it's a lot bigger. So this
tire is literally 1,000 lb. There's
four of them. So to bring it
over here, we thought it was going to
come on one trailer.
Single car trailer until we realized how
big it was, we had to go send the other
trailer.
Yeah, just tires. I plan to get like
three, four Can-Ams. Always wanted to do
this. We're going to walk into like
Yamaha or Honda or what what whoever has
everything that we want. I'm going to
walk in, I'm going to walk out with two
brand new Can-Ams, like four dirt bikes,
three ATVs. I'm going to be like, "Yo,
Ali, just finance them all of them. I
don't give a I'm a Trust me, I'm
approved." I I was looking online for
like 50 bucks a month for a dirt bike.
No way. Yeah, no 50 bucks a month zero
interest.
Zero interest? Why don't we have 50
right now? That's what I'm saying,
right? We just going to go in there AND
BE LIKE ALL OF THEM PUT THEM ON THE
TRUCK, BRO. It's free.
Oh, we have this thing. Remember? What
was the thing? Let's see if you
remember. What's free? When something is
[music] what? You don't pay for it. You
remember, right? He remembers. All
right, so what is it?
So anything under $100 is technically
free. It's technically free. Correct.
But if it's on a monthly basis it's
free. Anything under Anything Anything
under $100 is technically free. This is
where we plan.
As of right now, maybe it changes, maybe
it doesn't, but as of right now here we
plan to do
a drift track. A nice figure eight we're
going to do right around here. So I I
don't know how big the figure eight
should be, but there's so much wind.
Holy So I don't know how big the
figure eight should be, but we will do
it somewhere around here.
We should calculate it right now.
Oh, with the Miatas. Yeah, of course.
Okay.
I thought you were going to put out way
better, bro. Bro, I thought I was going
to squeeze out. Bro, I've always wanted
to do that. You got to have a more
gangster exit. Oh, should we do it
again?
>> Oh my god.
I was grass in my eyes, bro.
This is why we need a concrete drift
pad. But I didn't know concrete was
expensive. When you do a lot of it, it's
very expensive. I I'm getting like
quotes right now and I'm like, well,
construction is pretty expensive after
all. You know, I thought it was
inexpensive.
But yeah, we're going to do the figure
eight somewhere here. Uh I just don't
want to
get some type of
in my eye where then I can't see
the charts to make money.
Cuz then all this will be And
this will be more delayed.
>> Yeah, then this will be even more
delayed. See, I'm I'm I'm becoming more
responsible. I'm becoming a responsible
young adult. Am I not? Moving on over
here. So, this is going to be kind of
like a parking lot like back area
parking lot for guests. It's looking
like a junkyard right now. Right now,
yeah. Uh so, I bought a monster truck. I
think I said that already, right? Yeah.
Well, you only showed the wheels. You
never showed the actual truck.
>> we'll show the truck. Come on, let's see
it. So,
I just like buying cool Anything
that's cool and that's different, buying
it immediately, no questions asked.
Actually, I mean, you can tell. I got a
scoot seat, too.
So, this right here, ladies and
gentlemen, is my monster truck.
I don't know what the it is. I
think it has a big block Chevy old
engine,
carbureted.
Fiberglass shell of an old Camaro. This
is pretty much meant to
go crazy.
Like I'm talking, this is like a full
rust bucket. Look at this.
Yeah, I think I'd go crazy in there.
Yeah, long story short, this is a
bucket. It's a little project that we
have. Our goal is to like run over trees
with it with the big tires. With the big
tires, this ends up being like over
here. So, it becomes like a real monster
truck. For now, it's just here. I saw it
on Facebook Marketplace. I bought it
impulsively and I said, "Whatever."
Pick it up. So, now it's here. So, yeah,
over here there will probably be like a
20 35-car parking lot just to have the
space here. We're going to do some nice,
you know, clean division here with some
trees with a little path walkway to
everything else that we have it going on
over there. And then here is going to be
the paintball field. So, a paintball
field is actually really inexpensive and
very simple to build. You really just
need six poles or across the space that
you want to. You throw a big net and
then inside you can put whatever you
want. Some people say, "Oh, do the
speedball one." Honestly, I don't really
like the speedball. I like more of like
having random in there. Like we'll
probably put the beetle in there.
That'll be the the last place where the
beetle lands.
Um we'll probably put in there the jet
ski scooter, a container. Throw anything
in there so it's like an actual course
and you can be able to challenge your
friends because why would you want to do
speedball? I think speedball's pretty
Yeah, like hiding behind a little cone?
Like a cushion, you know? It's like,
dude, get in there like it was
war. I say that I I'm a camper myself,
bro. I'm just from the back. I'm like,
"I don't want to get shot." So, all this
is going to be a paintball field and
then over there, way over there, we're
going to have an actual helipad. So,
when all this is full of stuff and when
I go if I want to go in and out in a
helicopter, we can just
land over there. Hey!
Get to work! Come on!
Come on!
I pay my guys $8 a day.
No lunch included. Come on! Look at him.
Look at him. Look. What the is he
progressing on? Look at this guy.
Yeah, I mean if you want a job I'll pay
$8 a day. Um
with taxes not included so you will get
taxed on those $8. So, you realistically
get like $4. It's fair, man. You know,
it should be good nowadays, right? And
like that, ladies and gentlemen, I bring
you to the end of the tour of the Seven
Figure Estate of what we have right now.
There's a lot more that will be coming
in the next couple of months and I'm
doing everything as fast as I possibly
can. I don't want to be under
construction for a year. And you know
what? That that that's one of the things
that you know, it ties to exactly what I
was going to say right now. I was going
to say like, you know, when I started
this 7 years ago, this whole journey, I
I I I I I I I I I didn't think of having
a compound full of people trading or I
didn't think of becoming a trader. Like
that I I I just wanted to be successful
and then these things kind of stumble
across the way and you know, that that's
really been my journey the whole entire
time. People not believing in me, people
not supporting what I've done and I've
always just heard that opinion and and
I've done what I've wanted with that
opinion. A lot of people take
information from other people and it
dictates everything they're going to do.
But not me. like people right now said
that this was a terrible idea when I was
talking to some of my friends and family
a year ago of me doing this. I showed
them, you know, visions, showed them
renders of what I had in mind and people
didn't believe in it. They didn't
support it, they didn't think it was a
good idea. Fast forward to today, they
come in to see it in person, they think
it's a spectacular idea. And that that's
kind of what life and everything has has
consisted of for me. So, honestly for
me, I rather try and fail than not try
at all. Because what if it
does turn out great? What if it does
become into a half a billion dollar
fund? What if I do end up meeting great
successful traders and we do a bunch of
cool stuff here and a bunch of events?
Well, if I don't try, I'll never know.
And that's what I base my whole entire
life on, my whole entire decision-making
on. And the construction, people said,
"Oh, this is going to take you a year
and a half and a million dollars to do
it." Sure, but I'm going to do
everything in my power to get it done as
quick as possible and as cost-effective
as possible. If it takes me a million
bucks, it takes me a million bucks. If
it takes me a year, it takes me a year,
but I I want to do things correctly.
Longevity. Moral of the story, set it
and forget whatever the people are
going to say. People are going to
believe in you, some people are not.
Don't let that information dictate what
you're going to do. Get that information
and if it's not what you wanted to hear,
let it fuel you, let it motivate you to
exactly what you want to do in life and
who you want to be. And if you don't
have the clearest understanding of where
you want to be in the next year or two,
it's okay. You know, I've been in that
position. As as you develop and as you
stay consistent with who you want to be
at this very moment, new doors will open
up, new opportunities will come. But you
have to start. You have to take
that step and you have to move forward
because if not,
you're just going to stay in the exact
position where you are right now.
Remember, in order for things in your
life to change, you have to change
things in your life.
Simple.
With that being said, ladies and
gentlemen, welcome to whatever name you
guys give this. We will be back in
hopefully the next 3 months and all this
should potentially be done. Thank you
guys for being part of the video. I'll
see you guys in the next one.
>> [music]
>> Woohoo!
Woohoo!
>> [music]